<item>
<org>AlQaeda</org>
<date>June 20, 2009</date>
<location>35.46883,44.39098</location>
<desc>Truck bombing of a Shi’i mosque near Kirkuk blamed on Al Qaeda in Iraq: at least 75 killed, 163 wounded.</desc>
</item>
<item>
<org>AlQaeda</org>
<date>August 14, 2007</date>
<location>36.34,43.13</location>
<desc>Multiple truck bombings of two Yazidi villages near Sinjar in northern Iraq: at least 500 killed, approximately 1,500 wounded.</desc>
</item>
<item>
<date>March 6, 2007</date>
<location>29.606658,52.571709</location>
<desc>Two car bombings at a Shi’i shrine in Hilla: 106 killed.</desc>
 </item>
 <item>
<date>March 6, 2007</date>
<location>29.606658,52.571709</location>
<desc>Two car bombings at a Shi’i shrine in Hilla: 106 killed.</desc>
 </item>
<li  class="bk10"><em>November 23, 2006</em>: Series of car bombings and mortar attacks in the Shi’i Sadr City: at least 202 killed, approximately 250 injured. </li>

<li  class="bk10"><em>February 22, 2006</em>: Bombing of the Shi’i Al Askari Mosque in Samarra, which sparked a “civil war” between Sunnis and Shi’as in Iraq.</li> 

<li  class="bk10"><em>July 16, 2005</em>: Suicide car bomb struck a fuel tanker truck in Musayyib: at least 98 killed, 82 wounded. </li>

<li  class="bk10"><em>February 28, 2005</em>: Suicide car bombing in Hilla: at least 125 killed, 170 wounded.</li> 

<li  class="bk10"><em>October 24, 2004</em>: Coordinated vehicle bombings outside Baghdad’s Sheraton and Palestine hotels, which were frequented by members of the Western press: at least 20 killed.</li>   

<li  class="bk10"><em>May 17, 2004</em>: Suicide car bombing killed Governing Council President Izzedin Salim.</li> 


<li  class="bk10"><em>October 27, 2003</em>: Multiple car bombings at police stations and Red Cross Headquarters in Baghdad: 35 killed, 220 wounded. </li>

<li  class="bk10"><em>August 19, 2003</em>: Truck bombing at U.N. headquarters in Baghdad: 23 killed, including Sergio Vieira de Mello, the U.N. High Commissioner for Human Rights.</li>

<li  class="bk10"><em>August 7, 2003</em>: Bombing of the Jordanian Embassy in Baghdad: at least 11 killed, more than 50 injured.</li>
